<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Vault]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Vault</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 02:43:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 02:43:50 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[chill]]></title><description><![CDATA[sometimes i won't be dropping (shockhorrorwhoknew)
usually as a result of comfy aftercare &amp; a good transition, or if the play was not very intense or it wasn't one of the <a data-href="times i might need it!" href="aftercare/times-i-might-need-it!.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">times i might need it!</a>
hanging out together after is super useful if everything is going okay! if we both have time, spending it together casually &amp; talking about the play &amp; completely unrelated things helps to settle back into reality and act as a grounding method &lt;3
<br>let's yap! i love to dissect the plays and get into your brain / let you know my own thoughts. vv <a data-href="helpful" href="aftercare/helpful.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">helpful</a>.
]]></description><link>aftercare/chill.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Aftercare/chill.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 02:40:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[nonverbal]]></title><description><![CDATA[firstly - this doesn't necessarily mean that i am <a data-href="dropping" href="aftercare/dropping.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">dropping</a>, or that i will! it can happen just as a result of intense subbiness and the transition out of it.i likely will not be making much sense. my apologies! please don't be afraid, i am not angry at you nor am i trying to ignore you - i am just having some trouble connecting to words &lt;3<br>noise helps a lot!! when my brain gets too quiet / surroundings do in sensitive states - this is usually when <a data-href="dropping" href="aftercare/dropping.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">dropping</a>, or <a data-href="PTSD" href="aftercare/ptsd.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">PTSD</a> responses can sneak in
if you're a yapper -this is a great time to infodump about hyperfixations or tell me about smth you don't get to talk about a lot
reading aloud has also worked really well! fills up the quiet space in mind without forcing audible conversation &amp; let's me come out of it naturally/in my own time
playing music or streaming something can be helpful in place of you talking also if that is not something you enjoy/feel comfy doing - or continuing to talk to me via text. basically trying to avoid tew much empty space / making it a chill space we can exist in together until it passes this is especially helpful if it is something i already connect to (or fixate on) - my excitement at the things themselves - the music/streamed thing/thing you are talking about can supersede the nonverbal and bring me back a lot faster! ]]></description><link>aftercare/nonverbal.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Aftercare/nonverbal.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 02:33:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[dropping]]></title><description><![CDATA[
mood drops can be accompanied by a lack of clear emotion in speech and text will often be found with heart emotes like this - usually ones that lack colour or excitement <img alt="stoopid-emotes.png" src="aftercare/stoopid-emotes.png" target="_self">
not always something i will notice happening, but tone &amp; emotes are often a good indicator when trying to gage the situation can be characterised by a sense of detachment &amp; sometimes dissociation - will be fairly clear to those around me and eventually to me as well - emptiness/hollowness are key parts of it
can be temporary &amp; short-lived right after a scene, but may be delayed to several hours later or even the next day depending on intensity talk to me like a normal person please &lt;3 making this a big deal will go the opposite direction you may want!
<br>this may follow if a scene ended via a safeword or if i had brainworms about aspects of the scene - if you are aware of any of this then affirmations around those topics will be incredibly helpful, if, and only if they are accurate. (<a data-href="please god no" href="aftercare/please-god-no.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">please god no</a> heavy praise or flattery)
]]></description><link>aftercare/dropping.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Aftercare/dropping.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 02:14:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="aftercare/stoopid-emotes.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;aftercare/stoopid-emotes.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PTSD]]></title><description><![CDATA[CSA (childhood sexual assault) &amp; general SA trauma is a major thing in my past
can be triggered in ways that are unrelated to the scene
unless explicitly told - triggering this is NOT your fault bringing in pity/sympathy
calling me 'brave' for what happened
pressing for details
expressing wishes of violence to my family &amp;/or others that have harmed me
treating me as fragile or easily breakable - OR IN ANY WAY LIKE A CHILD
telling me that what is happening 'is not real' can take the form of flashbacks, hallucinations, hyperventilating etc. varies often - sometimes will just lead into a normal drop.
in the worst of situations i might not be able to recognise much outside of what i can see/hear/feel - i am not ignoring you on purpose.
often accompanied by high levels of guilt/shame/embarrassment - likely to receive a lot of apologies in this time - through text if my speech is unintelligible or not present (<a data-href="nonverbal" href="aftercare/nonverbal.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">nonverbal</a>)
after it passes - i will want to talk about how you feel &amp; figure out how to go from there. i strongly dislike people being around for this so if it becomes too much for you at any point - this is fully understandable! please do not feel weird about needing to take a step back and/or leave - i would much prefer that than for you to stick around in a way that could scare you or negatively affect you!
if you do decide to - you being there is already doing a lot if you are someone i am comfortable with. reminds me i am not alone &amp; existing with you will often make it last for a shorter period / be less intense. i know sometimes this can feel like you aren't doing enough or want to help, but truly this is all you can do! it is one of the things that will pass with time &amp; is a trauma response as opposed to a logical thing grounded in reality.
]]></description><link>aftercare/ptsd.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Aftercare/PTSD.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 01:41:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[please god no]]></title><description><![CDATA[
especially if i am dropping, try to avoid throwing in words like 'little', 'baby' or anything of the sort, even if you don't think those relate to that. in that headspace this can bring up <a data-href="PTSD" href="aftercare/ptsd.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">PTSD</a> related things and make it worse xx i know this is something lots of subs like, i understand how helpful this can be! but please for the love of god. tell me to get water or smth instead!! can interact with disordered eating behaviours. at most, a gentle reminder if i have snacks or food around - but please don't make it an obligation. <br>this can feel flattering, or fake. reassurances are super <a data-href="helpful" href="aftercare/helpful.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">helpful</a>, if they are accurate, but please don't say things for the sake of it or go overboard because you want me to feel better. vagueness, or fawning can increase the anxieties you may be trying to quell, or squash trust that you would tell me if something was wrong &lt;3
heavy praise makes me feel too much like i am filling a role once again, which is the opposite of what i want. similarly, i do not usually really want lots of cuddles/kisses &amp; things like this this can be context dependant, but in general, i take things very literally right after a scene - so it's something to be mindful of if that's not your intended reaction. often my speech will be unintelligible following play &amp; i may not be able to move very much! demanding or placing expectations on those things will cause them to take longer to return &amp; can lead to feelings of disappointment &amp; failure &lt;3 <br>once we have moved into aftercare, there needs to be a clear separation between play &amp; us as people. if i'm crying or unable to speak, sexualising this can trigger <a data-href="PTSD" href="aftercare/ptsd.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">PTSD</a> responses
using the clicker on the vc soundboard is also v unhelpful - will make me more subby and that is the opposite of the goal here!
well aware lots of subs are okay with horny aftercare but for whatever time we are remaining horny - i'm gna need some time after that to get back to normal. entirely fine to talk about other plays you have had another time, but during play &amp; aftercare please don't bring in comparisons !
]]></description><link>aftercare/please-god-no.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Aftercare/please god no.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 01:38:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[helpful]]></title><description><![CDATA[
if i'm intensely subby, i won't want to assume/do things without asking - &amp; brain fog can make me forget these are the next steps to take at all! i can get in my head if things feel fake or put on - just be yourself &amp; try to be as direct/upfront as you can - &amp; i'll try to do the same. i want to know ALL of your thoughts. what did you like? what didn't you like? specificity is good here. <a data-href="please god no" href="aftercare/please-god-no.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">please god no</a> veer away from flattering/intense praise! <br>if we are both feeling good this can be in the moment - if i'm <a data-href="nonverbal" href="aftercare/nonverbal.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">nonverbal</a> or <a data-href="dropping" href="aftercare/dropping.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">dropping</a> this can be difficult - in those cases talking about it later and/or the next day is great
point to specific elements in play!
ask questions, let me know if you want clarification, if things could be different for another time let me do the same
when done well this brings security to playing with you, let's me know you'll communicate things that you dislike &amp; helps me understand how to move forward. eliminates lots of anxieties! if it was a scene involving misgendering - this includes anything related to continued use of solely she/her pronouns or referring to me as a girl - this is super helpful &amp; grounding. reminds me you don't see me like that &amp; that you recognise me as a person etc. if you make a mistake, that's totally fine. happens a lot! best thing to do is not to make it a big deal - it won't be unless it's turned into one! <br>also ref <a data-href="nonverbal" href="aftercare/nonverbal.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">nonverbal</a> / <a data-href="dropping" href="aftercare/dropping.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">dropping</a> / <a data-href="PTSD" href="aftercare/ptsd.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">PTSD</a> for specifics in those situations.]]></description><link>aftercare/helpful.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Aftercare/helpful.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 01:36:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[README]]></title><description><![CDATA[hi! this is an aftercare document for indi/fairy/sol! if you're reading this then hopefully this can help to explain what might happen on my end, what sort of things are helpful, and how things can play out. oftentimes i will get <a data-href="nonverbal" href="aftercare/nonverbal.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">nonverbal</a> in aftercare, or may just be unintelligible - so i hope this can help communicate in my absence of ability!aftercare is a big deal - and i struggle to accept it or to feel like it is not a burden to engage it. i hope this can help you gage what it might be like, and come into things with an informed perspective on if you actually want to play with me and the extent you want to take things to &lt;3. <br>firstly it's probably good to have a look at <a data-href="times i might need it!" href="aftercare/times-i-might-need-it!.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">times i might need it!</a> generally, i do prefer these forms of play, but as they feel more intense that means the later steps will be the same.<br>while there are some things that are going to be <a data-href="helpful" href="aftercare/helpful.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">helpful</a>, or a <a data-href="please god no" href="aftercare/please-god-no.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">please god no</a> in most situations, it can also take different routes, from <a data-href="chill" href="aftercare/chill.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">chill</a>, to <a data-href="dropping" href="aftercare/dropping.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">dropping</a>, to times that my <a data-href="PTSD" href="aftercare/ptsd.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">PTSD</a> may rear it's head, &amp; if the <a data-href="nonverbal" href="aftercare/nonverbal.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">nonverbal</a> headspace comes into play. ]]></description><link>aftercare/readme.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Aftercare/README.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 23:17:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[stoopid-emotes]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="aftercare/stoopid-emotes.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>aftercare/stoopid-emotes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Aftercare/stoopid-emotes.png</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 22:31:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="aftercare/stoopid-emotes.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;aftercare/stoopid-emotes.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[times i might need it!]]></title><description><![CDATA[aftercare can look different depending on what we engaged with in the play! an understanding of this will build the more we play, but this is for a rough guide. examples of times it's definitely useful:
voiceplay - especially if consistently on vc for extended periods
cucking &amp;/or plays that involve other subs
scenes that might pull from my <a data-href="PTSD" href="aftercare/ptsd.html#_0" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">PTSD</a>, or trauma related play
intense painplay
overstim play and/or multiple goes of cumming &lt;3
appearance degradation TBA
if the play is mostly roleplay based, text based etc, it's less likely for me to experience a drop or need extensive aftercare. that's not to say there won't be exceptions, but it pulls on my emotions in a different way &lt;3]]></description><link>aftercare/times-i-might-need-it!.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Aftercare/times i might need it!.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 19:33:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>